1260 years prophetic time okay the Bible
is pointing out here that God would send
two witnesses that would prophesy for
1260 days we know that these two
witnesses therefore cannot be two human
beings because people don't live twelve
hundred and sixty years this is
prophetic time day for a year so these
two witnesses must be something else
what are those two witnesses everyone
the old and the New Testament the Bible
says search the scriptures for these are
they which testify of me what do
witnesses do they testify so you got the
Old Testament and the New Testament
doing their work of witnessing for
Christ during the 1260 years now please
follow along here phille II the Bible
goes on to say in Revelation 11 and
verse 4 these are the two olive trees
and the two candlesticks before the god
of the earth verse 7 when they shall
have finished their testimony so pause
right here when would they be finishing
their testimony at the end of the 1260
years so we're looking for something to
occur around the end of the 1700s so far
so good watch more carefully the Bible
says when they shall have finished their
testimony the Beast that ascendeth out
of the bottomless pit shall make war
against them and shall overcome them and
kill them and their dead bodies shall
lie in the street of the great city
which is spiritually called Sodom and
and where everyone one more time where
everyone Egypt where also our Lord was
crucified and they are the people and
Kindred's and tongues um and nations
shall see their dead bodies three days
and a half and shall not suffer their
dead bodies to be put in graves and they
that dwell on the earth shall rejoice
over them and make merry and shall send
gifts one to another because these two
prophets tormented them that dwelt on
the earth all right
so let's start right here point number
one
the this beast that rises up out of an
abyss what does a beast represent in the
Bible it represents a kingdom but what
does a beast typically represent in the
Bible it I mean what not what does it
represent what is a beast it's an animal
an animal is wild right a beast is a
wild animal I don't know if y'all are
catching this is wild it's not governed
by by order by law so so what we're
looking at here is a kingdom that would
come up on the scene just around or that
would come into prominence just around
the end of the 1260 years that would be
sort of like wild in nature it would it
would reject the Word of God the Old
Testament and the New Testament and they
would rejoice over the rejection of the
Word of God
what nation are we talking about friends
we're talking about the French
Revolution
all right so french revolution occurs
between the years 1799 t3 roughly to
about 1797 in fact it was the French
Revolution that actually brought about
the wounding of the papal power in 1798
exactly 1260 years as the Bible had
prophesied so I want to talk to you a
little bit about the French Revolution
are you ready are you ready are you sure
you're ready let's talk about the French
Revolution what was a French Revolution
the French Revolution was basically a
rebellion against the ancient regime I'm
not going to tell you what the ancient
regime is right right now but just keep
that term in mind ancient regime they
were against the ancient regime and they
want to change and so what ends up
happening is that during the French
Revolution
is a rejection of of religion of atheism
actually got its its its origin or its
push as it were from the French
Revolution they were tired of the of
what they had gone through with the
papacy during the Dark Ages and they
said enough is enough we don't want
anymore
but several things came as a result of
the French Revolution the first thing I
want you to to to to consider is that
that the the first time that the terms
left and right are used to represent
political ideology is you're in the
French Revolution the left was against
the ancient regime they want to change
let me share with you just a few things
about the left of the French Revolution
number one they were anti-clerical or
anti religion we don't even believe in
God anymore
the rise of atheism came from the French
Revolution not only were they anti
religion but during the French
Revolution there was a scientist by the
name of JB Lamarck JB Lamarque is the
first scientist to propose the idea that
man was not created instead he evolved
so they were anti religion and Pro
Evolution number three during the French
Revolution there was a man by the name
of marquis de sade anyone ever heard of
marquis de sade
marquis de sade is known as the father
of the sexual revolution marquis de sade
basically promoted the idea that a sex
was had nothing to do with god and one
could do whatever they wanted to do and
he actually promoted the idea of
homosexuality in fact during the French
Revolution guess what was outlawed I
mean guess what was legal
homosexuality so check this out guys I
don't know if you're catching this yet
the left was anti religion they were Pro
our evolution and they were Pro
homosexuality the left the left the left
not only were they not but check this
out I don't know I just discovered this
yesterday as I was putting my serving
together marquita saw the same marquee
the song marquis de sade again father
sexual revolution wrote promoted
pornography on a mass scale so check out
his name marquis de sade a father of the
sexual revolution marquis de sade may
have been the first to pen the idea that
abortion of a child was totally
legitimate even in its
reentry I never knew that so the left
during the French Revolution were anti
religion pro homosexual pro-abortion we
might say pro-choice man it sure is
quiet in here it sure is quiet yeah yeah
yeah god is good
God has shown us something guys listen
carefully not only were they these
things but also you may have known this
but the feminist movement had its origin
in the French Revolution
it's absolutely mind-blowing when you
when you study this out the the not only
that the feminist movement have its
origin in the in the French Revolution
uh uh
but also this did you know that during
the French Revolution uh they outlawed
slavery did you know that the French
colonies which were huge into slavery
was outlawed during the French
Revolution why because those involved in
the French Revolution saw the in
justices that were occurring under the
ancient regime and they said as a result
you know what you guys aren't doing it
so we're going to do it
you guys aren't caring about the poor
and and those suffering and and so we're
going to do it so it's very interesting
that that during the French Revolution
they were actually trying to do
something good but they were just trying
to do it without God we're going to care
about society we're going to care about
the poor because you guys aren't doing
it oh the church isn't doing it oh there
you are
then so since the church is not being
involved in in our day-to-day lives or
you know how we live in and and and our
suffering and our anguishes we reject
the
Church and we're going to do things
without God we're going to be moral
without God the left they promoted
secularism this is what rolls out of the
French Revolution the Bible says that
they rejoiced they rejoice over these
two witnesses now the question is why
why why was the French Revolution why
did the left by the way the left as I
stated earlier represented those who
were against the ancient regime the
right on the other hand represented
those who were for the ancient regime so
the question is why did the left why was
the left so why did they rejoice over
the the death as it were they outlaw the
Bible that's what it means by the death
of the two witnesses they outlawed the
Bible and here's a question who was the
ancient regime that they were rejoicing
over I invite you to turn with me to
Revelation chapter 13 Revelation chapter
13 verse 1 when you get there please say
Amen
revelation 13 verse 1 describes the
ancient regime that the left turned
against listen carefully the Bible says
and I stood upon the sand
in seven heads and ten horns and upon
his horns ten crowns and upon his heads
the name of blasphemy and the beats
which I saw was like unto a leopard his
feet were as the feet of a bear his
mouth as the mouth of a lion and the
dragon gave him his power his seat and
his great Authority and I saw one of his
heads as it were wounded to death and
his deadly wound was healed and all the
world wondered after the Beast verse
five there was given unto him a mouth
speaking great things and blasphemies
and power was given unto him to continue
forty two months twelve hundred and
sixty days or prophetic years therefore
this beast that is seen rising up out of
the sea represents the same power back
in Daniel chapter 7 that religion
political power that dominated during
twelve hundred and sixty years this was
the ancient regime it was the papacy
those are that power that had dominated
politics and religion over all Europe
including friends so here's a question
why did the Left rebel against the right
did you catch my question just now why
did the left in France rebel against the
ancient regime well let me tell you why
because this was supposed to be the
Church of God but what was the Church of
God doing during the Dark Ages they were
they were oppressing the poor they were
sanctioning persecution oppression
slavery they were not caring about the
poor the needy the suffering and as a
result of this the left says well if
not what if that's what Christianity is
then we don't want anything to do with
it you see whatever listen carefully
during this 1260 years you had the
church who was claiming to stand for God
and yet being hypocritical by the way
that they treated society so if you can
just imagine the left going wait a
minute you claim to be of God and yet I
mean just imagine the the politics of
the religion just imagine the politics
of the right just imagine what must have
gone on as they were supposedly standing
for God but would allow certain things
but in the name of God how much that
turned the left of mass question do you
see that happening today in our religion
do you see people who are supposed to be
standing for God all right you know let
me let me speak frankly here uh you know
I would expect I'm just just you know
please don't stole me I love you whoever
you are and whoever you stand for right
now I love you but but for me to to hear
the left
you know degrade the right which which
happens yes you know oh yeah you know
what they do this and they do that and
we looked into their records and we saw
this and we saw that day you know to
hear that you know I'm good with that
because guess what the left is not
really about God anyway not only in
everyone I'm just saying as a whole it's
it's you know anti religion it's it's
you know Pro Evolution it's you know
everything that the Bible says not that
does that we can explain that away so
pro homosexuality Pro everything right
so I can understand the
that's not having the same standard as
Christian should have are you with me so
when I see in here Christians who are
supposed to be standing for Christ using
methods that can be nothing more stated
in no other way but as the methods of
Satan lies our mishandling of truth
manipulation of people I just say how
what must unless be thinking as they're
saying and wait a minute you're you're
the ones that represent Jesus I mean I
look at these rallies and I see on the
right and please believe me I'm not
trying to influence anybody I'm just
speaking as a Christian okay I'm
speaking as a 78 minutes I look and I
see the hatred and the vitriol coming
from supposing Christians and I'm like
no wonder the left is going left
no wonder the left believes nothing at
all about the Bible because as they look
at the example of those who are supposed
to be Christians no wonder no wonder and
so the the left rejected the ancien
régime why because they were doing these
very things now now I want you to check
this out check this out
the Bible tells us that this power
during the Dark Ages was Babylon that's
their name
yes spiritual Babylon now what does
Babylon do to the world what does it do
to the world it gives the world
something it gives it what wine it gives
it wine oh man I don't know if you guys
are ready for there are you ready for
this Seventh day Adventists and everyone
else whoever will visit are you ready
for this check this out we know that
dabble on gives the world run and makes
the world
drunk on wine and as Adventists we've
said all yeah you know that wine is that
wine is false what false doctrines are
false teaching and we say praise the
Lord as Adventists we are not drinking
the wine but but but oh my but
revelation - I'm sorry proverbs 20 verse
1 says wine is a mocker and strong drink
is ranging up listen carefully this is
what the verse is saying wine leads one
to mock give us see someone drunk and
what do they do a joint person doesn't
take things seriously a drunk person
mops a drunk person does not understand
the seriousness or the truth of
something so check this out
we might think that that that rhyme just
represents doctrine but listen France
have been drinking the wine of Babylon
for 1260 years and the result of
drinking wine is that they began to mock
ok they began mocking that which was
they began mocking the Word of God
what does wine do it leads us to not
take seriously it leads us to mock and
be a mockery and what happens that when
the French Revolution occurred and they
began mocking Christianity when the
reason the left began mocking
Christianity is because they had drunk
of the wine of Babylon for 1260 years
which means we love it that the reason
today that the left has rejected God is
because they have drunk the wine of
Babylon
the result of babylons
teachings during the Dark Ages the
result of their of their unbiblical
example is part of their line and as a
nation's drank this wine and perhaps
were forced to drink this wine the
result that you see wine doesn't kick in
immediately when you drink wine it takes
a little while before the effect starts
to occur in your mind and what happens
is that the French Revolution because
they had been drinking and drinking and
drinking the result is now they're like
God what God God right that was the
result they were drinking the wine of
Babylon and that led them to reject to
mock is a left mocking God today now
believe me please don't get me wrong I
don't mean every single individual that
I mean as a as a platform is the left
generally understood to be against the
Word of God they are mocking God why
because they have drunk of the wine of
Babylon
please hold that thought remember what I
just said and I want you to go with me
to Revelation chapter 13 because we're
going to see something else absolutely
amazing here revelation 13 Revelation
chapter 13 verse 11 when you get there
please say Amen revelation 13 verse 11
John says and I beheld another beast
coming up out of the earth he had two
horns like a lamb and he spake as a
dragon stop right here
contextually speaking this verse brings
us to the end of the 1260 years so
around 17 the late 1700s John now sees
another beast coming up out of the earth
a beast represents a nation or a kingdom
so here you have another nation coming
up out of the earth and it has horns
like a lamb but it speaks like
a dragon what do the what does the lamb
represent in the Bible represents Jesus
so what kind of a nation would we be
looking at to come upon the scene around
the late 1700s that would be a
christ-like nation the United States of
America but guys check this up
I mean praise the Lord and sort of
because listen carefully guys this power
is described as a lamb that speaks like
a dragon now beloved I don't know about
you but as I look at the history of the
United States of America from it's very
inception it has appeared like a lamb
but has spoken like a dragon it's a
beast oh it's a beast you tell me is
beast mode its beast mode yeah yeah this
is America in beasts mode but we haven't
seen anything yet because listen beloved
one America was wrong it was supposedly
the land of liberty for how many all
except black people and women and
Indians yeah in other words but I mean
this nation that was supposed to be yes
we are a Christian nation was reflecting
the very same character as the papacy of
the Dark Ages horns of a lamb speaking
like a dragon now got a question for you
how many of you like lambs sheep I like
sheep you know what kind of sheep I
don't like the ones that talk like
dragons I hate dragon like sheep you
know a sheep a lamb is supposed to be a
lamb which means when you get it you you
expect if you pit you expect to hear
back that's what I expect to hear when a
lamp opens it I do not expect to hear a
roar like a dragon so whatever listen to
me Wow
on the left you have this this this
power that is anti-god and is openly so
on the right you have this power that
claims to be for God but speaks like a
dragon and beloved let me tell you
something as I look at our political
landscape today and as I look at what
the left is doing and how they seem to
be wanting to to penetrate the church
and to you know make the church do you
know accept certain things that the
church cannot accept I can understand
that because that's what they're
supposed to do what I can't understand
and they can in a sense because it's
prophetic is for those who claim to the
Lamb like to speak like a dragon and in
fact what you will see that here is that
even in God's eyes God doesn't focus on
the beast from the abyss as much as he
does the beast from the earth why
because the beasts from the earth is
professing to speak in his name
God says look if you're going to do evil
just don't do it in my name I can I can
I can accept that I'll deal with you on
that level but the worst thing is to do
evil in my name this is what made the
papacy such an abomination to God
because they were doing evil in his name
and when you do Eva in his name what
that leads to is leftism oh if that's
who God is we want nothing to do with
him this is what God's do this is what
Satan is after I should say Satan is
trying to make God look crazy I mean I
cannot help but think that as a left
looks at what the so-called religious
right is doing they must be thinking
these people and their God is crazy it's
interesting that the left they were for
civil liberties they were for they were
for homosexuality they were for abortion
everything that the left stood for in
the French Revolution is what the left
stands for today and everything that the
right stood for in the French Revolution
is what the right stands for today
beloved it is mind-blowing but check
this out you see wine is not only a
marker it is also what it is also what
strong drink is what raging so not only
does wine cause mockery wine also causes
anger anger I am mad at what those
people are doing to our country look at
all these immigrants okay we got a shirt
for the air grants so let me take that
back no no you get the idea you know we
are angry at what is happening to our
Christian nation yes look at what's
going on look at what the left is doing
we are angry we are so angry it's like
we've drunk the wine you see beloved
listen not only this wine lead to a
mockery of God wine also leads to anger
and the way that Babylon is making the
whole world drink of her wine is that is
leading one group to the anti God
mocking and the other group to get so
agree that they will do things despite
who their God is they will do things in
the name of God against God and the
whole world is drinking the wine guess
what
including seventh-day adventists if you
don't believe me just get on Facebook
jump just look at the the spirit of
anger that is even permeating our very
own people wait who are you voting for
and now you didn't just say you vote you
can how can you have a seven-day attic
you see this spirit of anger is
permeating even our church am i telling
the truth see we think the wine of
Babylon is just false teaching no no no
no no wine is not only false teaching
wine is the result of an evil spirit it
is the result it leads to mocking or
anger and the question is what are you
doing right now
you see check this out do you know the
Bible says that the little horn the
papacy
his wound would be healed yes let me ask
something is is the papacy regaining
ground today yeah you want to know how
they're regaining ground this is
absolutely amazing how is it that
they're gaining that they're regaining a
validity in the eyes of the world how is
that even possible
and they answer that question will tell
you what we should be doing as a people
what are they doing what are they doing
love and acceptance can you give you
some other words like when you say love
like what do they like think about it
what makes the Catholic Church like
acceptable now to so many people what
are they doing specifically there what
did charity way what chart oh so they're
doing good for society they are they
helping the oppressed
are they ministering to the poor and the
needy oh wow so check this out in the
dark ages they what they had was
doctrine but no charity the left was
like nah
so now as they're coming back into power
guess what their guess what they're
using they're using charity but they
still don't have doctrine well but love
it the way I see it there's only one
group of people only one group of people
that have the doctrine yeah
who is that people it's God's remnant
but that one group of people apparently
are not doing something else it's found
in Isaiah 58 yet Isaiah 58 relieving the
oppressed loosing the bands of
wickedness is see beloved we have looked
at what the church did during the dark
ages we looked at what the religious
right is doing right now we're saying
yeah we don't want to get involved in
our we don't want to all we want to do
is preach the gospel but beloved unless
we're preaching the gospel
combined with ministering to our society
ministering to our community letting
them know look this is who God is God is
not one that does not care about the
poor and the oppressed he is one but
guess what God also has truth when we
bring these two things together
something powerful will begin to happen
we begin to replace counterfeit wine
with genuine wine with true wine with
true teaching but of it
God is looking for his people let me
tell you some you want to know who to
vote for how many of you like pastor who
should we vote for it I'm have you
already know who you're voting for don't
raise your hand
mm-hm eat Lu something if you want to
know who to vote for I'm not gonna tell
you who or what let me tell you the one
standard who are you ready everybody's
leaving for right now and what is he not
the same listen I said to my cyber
school class a little bit earlier today
in 1888 there was a Sunday law bill that
came before Congress now what do you
think Adventists would be happy about
that yes no I mean think about it
it's prophecy signs at the end the end
is near right Jesus is coming okay
but a man by the name of eighty Jones
Marilyn eighty Jones went to the
Congress on behalf of seventh-day
Adventists and argued against the Sunday
law why would he do such a thing why
would the church have such a sense of
arguing against something that they knew
would bring the end of the world why why
did they do that they needed more time
more time look give us more time to
finish the work so listen carefully when
you vote don't vote for Hillary don't
vote for Trump
vote for time whichever vote you think
is going to lead to giving us more time
as a people to finish the work then vote
that now I don't know who you think that
might be that's that's you that's up to
you and God but what you should be
voting for is Lord we were talking about
this today Desmond Doss
Desmond DOS yeah if you've seen the
hacksaw bridge trailer at the very end
of that trailer you hear Desmond Desmond
das saying give me one more Lord just
give me one more Desmond das wanted more
time to win one more that is what our
focus needs to be Lord give us time to
win one more now let me close with this
let me close with this America is about
to go into be smooth I believe it it's
going to go why it's going to go all out
it's gonna go quick and when America
goes into beast mode
you and I need to be ready we need to be
ready and listen when America goes into
beast mode it is going to mimic Babylon
during the dark ages that's what it's
going to do when it does that it goes
all out and what happens is according to
according to Daniel 11 verse 40 the cave
and the king of the south pushing
against the king of the north is going
to end with the king of the north coming
back with an overwhelming force against
the king of the south so right now the
king of the witch you know what you see
happening right now
the king of the south is pushing further
and further against the king of the
north the king of the north when it
pushes back is going to totally
overwhelm the left so here's what I'm
telling you okay if Hillary Clinton wins
this election you thought the right was
angry now wait until
wait until at if the right winds right
now it's trouble either way it's trouble
either way but what what the prophecy
tells us is that the the right Babylon
will overthrow Egypt spiritually and
then turn its focus on the remnant do
you know there's another place in the
Bible where that except the exact thing
happened do you know that the literal
kingdom of Babylon Nebuchadnezzar
kingdom before he overthrew before he
turned his attention to Israel you know
who yet over the room he had just
overthrown just defeated Egypt and after
he defeated Egypt he turned his focus on
Israel in other words Babylon went be
smooth well who survived that beast mode
of Babylon Daniel yeah
all right so transaction will end in our
closing closing minutes here okay if we
want to know how to stand when America
goes beast mode and all we need to do is
look how Daniel stood when Babylon went
beast mode so check this out ready I'll
just do this one of it in Daniel chapter
one
Daniel avoids the wine of Babylon if you
want to stand in this time when America
is going beast mode avoid the wine avoid
the wine
yeah Adventist that doesn't mean I'm
going to end up mocking God for
Adventist that means I am so angry that
means you begin to partner up with the
very religious right that you know is a
beast that looks like a lamb but it's
going to speak like a dragon avoid the
what are we doing what are we doing
backing up the sentiments of the
religious right really
this same power I mean I get the
principles I get the principles you know
we can stand for we should be no you
know for the saving of life and we
should be for what the Bible says it's
true but beloved standing with a
political party that has no clue no no
no no avoid the line because you see
wine doesn't hit you immediately you
might think yeah I'm Adventist and I
know when to pull away but wine kind of
whosoever is deceived thereby is not
wise you might be drinking on like I got
it I got it I got it man I got it I got
Emma and the next thing you know you are
lockstep with the beast that rises from
the earth so in Daniel 1 he avoids the
wine of Babylon just as at the end of
time God is going to have a people who
avoid the wine of Babylon and as a
result in Daniel 2 they are the ones
that are able to preach with power the
message that Babylon will fall because
that's what happens in Daniel 2 Babylon
is prophesied to fall well as a result
of this preaching in Daniel 3 he sets up
an image to the Beast he sets up an
image to the kingdom just as at the end
of time because of a people who will
stand against the wine of Babylon will
preach with conviction that Babylon will
fall as a result Babylon itself will set
up an image and command all to bow down
in Daniel 4 you have Babylon sins
reaching onto heaven just as at the end
of time when when spiritual Babylon does
this her sins will reach on the heaven
in Daniel 5 you have the message that
Babylon is fallen just as at the end of
time Babylon will fall in Daniel 6 you
have a death decree given to Daniel he
is put in a tomb
sealed but by the grace of God Daniel
overcomes the death decree just as at
the end of time there will be a death
decree in which the people of God who
refuse to bow down to the laws of the
land will be will be commanded be put to
death but just as Daniel overcame the
death penalty so God's people at the end
of time will overcome in Daniel 7 the
little horn
will have his Dominion taken away in
Daniel 8 the sanctuary will finally be
cleansed in Daniel 9 that which is
determined will be poured out upon the
desolate in the plagues in Daniel 11 he
will come to his end Satan will come to
his end and none can help him and in
Daniel 12 Michael will stand up deliver
his people and they which are in the
ground shall rise up to meet those in
the air and so shall we ever be with the
Lord you want to learn how to stand when
America goes beast mode don't drink the
wine don't get caught up in the anger of
the left or the anger of the right don't
get offended by the mockery of the left
keep your eye on Jesus know that you
have been put here to to reflect the
character of Christ and that means not
only as a church should we be preaching
the doctrine but we should also be
ministering and showing them we are not
a church that doesn't care about our
neighbor and they're there their plight
their needs yes we're going to get
involved in helping people in a society
who are oppressed whether it's because
of their race or their yes we're going
to help we are going to be a part of
we're going to show you that we care and
we're going to reveal to you that Christ
is in us as a church because his
character is demonstrated by our care
for the oppressed so beloved our hope
that as you as you have listened to the
message today it is my prayer that you
do not drink the wine do not drink the
wine remember who we are as a people
stand for Jesus vote for time and then
when and if God gives us that time do
everything we can as a church to reflect
who Jesus really is heavenly father
America Protestant America it seems as
if it is truly going beast mode right
now there is anger there is hatred there
is vitriol there is hypocrisy and Lord
on the left the left is there because as
Christians we fail to represent who you
really are the left is the fault of
Christianity and then we want to try to
fix the left by misrepresenting you even
more oh lord please snap us out of this
delusion and Lord as Adventists may we
not partake of the wine may we instead
reflect your character nor remind us
that Isaiah 58 calls us not only to
preach the gospel but also to minister
to be oppressed to reach out to them and
to show them that we care about their
oppression lower their people who are
locked up in prison right now who have
no business being there how can we as a
church help them there are people who
are being oppressed because of the color
of their skin they're people who are
being oppressed because there
from this country Lord how can we
minister to them Lord please teach us
that even people's whose behavior we
disagree with should not be oppressed
but we should find ways to minister to
them to win them into your truth you
have no part of oppression and so lord
please please before time runs out show
us as a church how to truly reflect your
character forgive us Lord for even
sipping of the wine and lord help us
help us to be like Jesus this is our
prayer in your name we pray amen